Hello everyone!
Welcome to Kimi no Heart!
We are Doki Michi Senri!
Yay!
So today...
What will we be doing at the Josho TV?
What is it?
We will be having a diagnosis.
A diagnosis?
What is it?
We're having a meeting today, so we're
all excited.
I'm looking forward to it.
So, can we call you in?
Yes!
So, Mr. Kihara!
Mr. Kihara!
Yay!
Hello!
Nice to meet you!
Thank you!
Today, I will answer the personality
test called Digram diagnosis.
I will give you the results of the
diagnosis.
What is this Digram diagnosis?
It is a new type of personality test
that combines psychology, statistics,
data, and the heart of a human being.
Please take a look at the summary
section for the details of the Digram
diagnosis.
But satan just came out.
At times like these, something good
should be delivered.
The evil souls who make everyone rage
like so.
For their trials of mono directions to
come,
This program is a program in which six
people who are active to promote
something exciting challenge various
things to raise the excitement value of
the world.
Please register your channel.
By the way, you all did self-analysis
before you got diagnosed, right?
Yes.
Please tell us if you know your
personality well.
Your personality...
You just wrote your answer, right?
You wrote your answer.
What is it?
You're a normal person, right?
No, no, no!
No!
What kind of personality do you think
you have?
Do you know your personality well?
No, I don't.
I'm not good at talking.
I only know that.
I see.
Today, I can see your current
personality.
Oh, thank you.
It's very important.
You're going to be an idol and a social
person.
You're going to be an idol, right?
How do you want people to see you?
I see.
Today, I want you to finish it with a
clear mind.
I want to do it.
Let's do it.
Let's get rid of the confusion.
I want to get rid of it.
Let's get started.
I'm looking forward to it.
If you analyze the six of us, we are
all good.
We are all good.
We are all bright.
We analyze various groups.
We are all different.
Some are dark, some are a little bit
shy.
But we are all bright.
We are all bright.
Some are a little bit shy.
Many.
I want to evaluate you based on these
points.
Let's start with the first one.
Tsujino Kanami.
I'll give you a word of advice.
Tsujino is a pain in the neck.
I'm in trouble.
Let's start with the first one.
You are careful about how people look
at you.
But you are very innocent when you get
along with people.
I'm in trouble.
It takes time to get along with people.
You are not logical.
You are intuitive.
You have a lot of ideas.
You are quick to do what you want to
do.
I'm quick to do what I want to do.
That's why you are like a persimmon.
I know that.
You have a lot of hobbies.
What are your hobbies?
I cook, do accessories, do postcards,
and do many other things.
But I'm not good at it.
I'm not good at it.
You must be worried about it.
I feel like I should try it since it's
autumn.
I think you are more than 10 times more
satisfied with your life than last year.
I want to be satisfied.
Today is a clear day.
Do you have a diary?
I used to have it.
I'm sorry.
I think you are not satisfied with your
life since it's autumn.
I'm not satisfied.
I wrote a diary.
You don't have to write it for a long
time.
For example, you can write a diary on
Twitter.
You can write a diary about how many
points you got today.
If you keep writing it for 3 months, it
will be logical.
It will be logical.
It means you are a good woman who can
see the future.
I'm a good woman.
If you can do that, you won't feel like
it's autumn.
And you will be confident.
I want to be confident.
If you can, you can add the points you
got in 3 months and get an average
score.
I'm confident.
If you look back at your score in 3
months, you can get a lot of ideas and
it's actually a good thing.
Wow, that's amazing.
It's like a god's magic.
It's not. It's data. I'm not taking it
for myself.
Do you have any questions?
I'm not sure.
I want to speak, but I can't because
I'm nervous.
You talk a lot when you're in a good
mood.
That's right.
So, when you're in a good mood, you
talk a lot.
I see.
Then you won't be in a bad mood.
Well,
I have no words to describe.
Thank you.
You don't have a lot of personality.
I'm a normal person.
You have a very unique personality.
That's a good point.
I'm not a normal person.
Normal people are not here.
Next is Bambi Fujimoto.
I'm a lonely person.
I'm a strong person.
I have a strong heart.
You have a strong heart.
You are doing what you want to do.
You are a stubborn person.
You are a lonely person.
You are not satisfied with yourself.
You are not a lonely person.
You are a stubborn person.
You are doing what you want to do.
You are kind.
Why do you say that?
I'm glad.
You are upset.
You are not understanding yourself.
You have a problem.
I think you have various emotions.
You can change your personality
depending on the situation.
I'm scared.
You have a little bit of a heavy
personality.
I'm not saying you are bad.
You can change your personality.
I'm scared.
Do you have any worries?
I'm in the third year of junior high
school now, but I was very confident in
myself when I was in elementary school.
I was confident in doing various
things, but when I became a junior high
school student, I met various people and
lost my confidence.
You lost your confidence.
I have one point.
I prepared the best part.
This is a very childish world.
You are energetic and have a strong
energy to do what you want to do.
So, when you are in trouble, don't say,
I don't care.
There are few people in the world who
can say,
I don't care.
I think there are only three people in
the world.
I think there are many people who have
been hit by a tough wall.
It's good to say, I don't care.
I understand. Thank you.
It would be funny if Bambi said that.
I would be very confused.
I would be like, I don't care.
I agree.
Sakai-san.
I was nervous by myself.
What do you think of your personality?
What kind of personality?
I want to decide and train myself.
Why?
I don't know.
Among these 6, Sakai-san has a
characteristic personality.
She is a person who loves herself.
I love myself.
You are laughing.
I can't see you from here.
Women like this kind of personality.
It's a mascot.
Good.
She is a good person.
She is loved by everyone.
She has a high probability of becoming
a mascot.
I love myself.
You are laughing.
It's a good meaning.
It's not a bad meaning.
I love myself.
I like myself, so I like others.
I'm a person who is a little
mischievous.
That's not good.
I'm a little mischievous.
What?
You are mischievous.
I'm a little mischievous.
I sometimes overdo it.
You are loved by everyone.
You are a person who can be helped.
You are a person who can balance well.
You are not particular about anything.
That's right.
You are not strict.
You can accept anything.
That's great.
You are like a white Tiramisu.
I am an Afro-type guy.
Please look at that.
I am cool, right?
I am wearing this to look good for you.
It's raining.
My hair is a bit messy.
I am cool with messy hair.
Juran.
How is it?
My umbrella.
It's good.
Do you want to touch it?
Everyone is going to be crazy.
Where is Hitokadono?
Hitokadono is here.
Hitokadono.
This is me.
We are shooting the rising moon in real
time.
Rising.
Oharu is here.
I'll go.
Every time I think of the moon, I feel
anxious.
I'm here to set up the center instead
of Hitokadono.
Hitokadono is good at setting up the
center.
I hate the moon.
So I'll change the center.
No way.
There was a big battleground in the
place where the camera couldn't see.
My stomach is suddenly full.
Julia is here.
What's that face?
It's a good scene.
Julia is here.
She did Aori.
Yes, Aori.
It's a heart-pounding... No, it's a
crazy girl.
It's a crazy boy.
It was cute.
It was really cute.
You feel so good.
One, two, three.
I'll go.
I'm going to go.
What?
I'm going.
My hands are cold.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
Don't care.
Let's start eating the main course.
First, fresh vegetables.
Cook in the medium heat for about 40
seconds then wait for it to get soft.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you!
It was a really hard work.
It's been about 2 months since February
to April.
It's really fast.
It was fast.
Thank you for your hard work.
Every time, I saw the first corner of
Piyo.
It was fun.
I was excited.
Today is the last day of February.
Today, on January 14th,
we will celebrate our half-year
anniversary.
Congratulations!
6 months!
Cute!
Thank you!
Please continue to support us!
Please watch our video!
Please watch!
I'm not alone, I'm not alone
One, two, three
This song is for you, call me, call me
Let's go forward with our voices out
loud, high-five!
If you're feeling down, then let's go
together
One, two, three
Anything can be overcome
Go! To the future!